quizrocket.com 2012-10-15

# Privacy Policy

At Quiz Rocket, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect from you to personalize your experience in accordance with your preferences. We only sell, trade or rent your personal information to other parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy and your preferences. 

Please read the following details of our Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to users of the Quiz Rocket network of web sites, and applies to all sites on the domain quizrocket.com. Information collection, use and protection of personally identifiable information (referred to hereafter as "PII") and the choices you have concerning PII are described in this policy. Quiz Rocket is controlled by Miva AK, Inc, 4600 Madison, 10th Floor, Kansas City, MO 64112. 

**By using Quiz Rocket you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy also applies to users that have agreed to receive e-mail marketing from Quiz Rocket and joint marketing advertisers ("Advertisers") that collaborate with Quiz Rocket, whether at Quiz Rocket, via email, on third party websites, via co-registration or otherwise.**

  * I. Collected Information
  * II. Use Of Collected Information
  * III. Information Sharing and Disclosure
  * IV. Preferences/Opt-Out
  * V. Third Parties
  * VI. Security
  * VII. Accessing and Updating Personal Information
  * VIII. Data Integrity
  * IX. Children 

We regularly review our compliance with this Policy. Quiz Rocket may edit this Policy from time to time. When we make substantial changes to uses of PII, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice on our privacy policy, as well as an indicator on the home page of Quiz Rocket. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy via postal mail to Miva AK, Inc, 4600 Madison, 10th Floor, Kansas City, MO 64112. When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is our policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. 

## I. Collected Information

**Registration:** Registration is required to participate in Quiz Rocket quizzes, or in any other promotion or contests run by Quiz Rocket. You will be asked for PII as part of the registration process. Quiz Rocket requires that a user be thirteen (13) years of age or older, except in the state of Maine, where a user must be eighteen (18) years of age or older. PII collected at registration may include email address, telephone number, gender, birth date, age, street address, home town, country and postal code. 

**Additional PII:** Additional PII may be collected through use of the site including responses to questions, taking quizzes, surveys or polls, or through various offers provided on site. Quiz Rocket may collect and retain PII relating to email marketing sent to, and opened by, users on our marketing list(s). Quiz Rocket may additionally run promotions that may ask for additional demographic data. 

**Other Information:** In addition to PII, additional information may be collected, such as system information, browser type (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), IP address, the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS), what version of Adobe Flash you are using (e.g., Flash 9.0), CPU type (e.g. Pentium), your manner of connecting to the Internet (e.g., connection speed through narrowband or broadband access), information about your geographic location, and the domain name of your Internet service provider. We also track some of the pages that you visit on our Website through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs). This tracks usage information about users who have received targeted promotional campaigns. In addition, Quiz Rocket uses third-party service provider partners to employ anonymous cookies for accounting and data integrity purposes. 

**Other sources:** We may receive information about you from other sources, including publicly available information or information available from third party sources, such as updated delivery and address information from our carriers or third parties, and add it to our account information, generally for updating purposes. We may also obtain information about you through optional co-registration and/or advertisements on sites operated by third parties. 

**Cookies:** Cookies are pieces of data stored in the browser's memory or written to the user's hard drive that provide the ability to recall information across user sessions. This also enables tracking of various user actions and helps customize the display of site content and personalized advertisements. Most web browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. You do not have to accept cookies to use Quiz Rocket, but Quiz Rocket may not work correctly if cookies are disabled, and some functionality may be completely unavailable. You may reset your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to reject cookies generally. The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable cookies altogether. 

You can request that we stop storing cookies on your computer, and that we don't set any more. **Please be aware that if you decline the use cookies set by Quiz Rocket, you will be unable to use the site.**

Click here to opt-out of Quiz Rocket cookies

## II. Use of Collected Information 

**Marketing:** PII you submit to Quiz Rocket remains your property, but by submitting PII to Quiz Rocket you grant Quiz Rocket the right to use that information for marketing purposes including: 

  * Sharing such information whether at Quiz Rocket, via email, on third party websites, via co-registration or otherwise with Advertisers
  * Delivering certain direct marketing offers to you via telemarketing, e-mail marketing, direct mail, SMS messaging and other types of direct marketing unless you request for this information not to be disclosed to third parties for marketing purposes using the opt out below or you have previously opted out from your PII being disclosed to third parties for marketing purposes. 

Your PII is used in a variety of other ways, including: 

  * Ensuring better presentation of site content to match demographic interests
  * Customizing advertising on the site [in accordance with your preferences]
  * Improving the site
  * Contacting you regarding Quiz Rocket (including your registration with Quiz Rocket)
  * Fulfilling prizes
  * Tracking compliance with our Quiz Rocket Rules
  * Improving content and feedback purposes
  * Confirming user registration with Quiz Rocket and co-registration with Advertisers
  * Combining with information from third party sources 

## III.Information Sharing and Disclosure

We only share PII with other companies or individuals outside of Miva AK, Inc in the following limited circumstances: 

**Third Party Service-Providers:** Quiz Rocket may from time to time share email addresses and other PII with third parties to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending informational emails about our products and services. In these cases, Quiz Rocket uses only trusted partners who have entered into non-disclosure agreements prohibiting use or dissemination of PII and that meet the requirements set out in the Security section below. 

**Third Party Marketers:** We may sell PII you supply to us to selected third parties for direct marketing purposes, unless you request for this information not to be disclosed to third parties for marketing purposes using the opt out below or you have previously opted out from your PII being disclosed to third parties for marketing purposes. These businesses may include, providers of direct marketing services via telemarketing, e-mail marketing, direct mail, SMS messaging and other types of direct marketing. 

**Other Third Parties:** We may sell PII you supply to us to other selected third parties, including providers of applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation. 

**Protection of Miva AK, Inc. and others:** We reserve the right to access, use, preserve or disclose PII: as required by law , regulation, legal process or governmental request and when we believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure is necessary to protect our or our users' rights, property or safety and / or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, legal process or governmental request served upon our company; enforce the terms and conditions of Quiz Rocket, including investigation of potential violations; and to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information about our user base with partners and advertisers, and to run promotions [in accordance with your preferences], and this may include demographics, usage, or characteristics of Quiz Rocket participants as a group. We may also share with Advertisers usage information about users who have received targeted promotional campaigns, for the purpose of formatting future campaigns and upgrading user information used in reporting statistics in accordance with your preferences. This information is collected by tracking some of the pages you visit on Quiz Rocket through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs). 

**Merger/Acquisitions:** If Miva AK, Inc. becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before PII is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

## IV. Preferences/Opt Out

If you provide us with your address, telephone number and/or email, you may receive occasional mailings, phone calls, or emailings from us or our agents with information on Miva AK, Inc, new products, industry news, product features, and upcoming events. We send promotional email to our users, including users who have not opted out after having received promotional email from us. 

To the extent we use PII to email you about our products and services, our email practices are in compliance with the U.S. SPAM laws. 

If you do not wish to receive promotional communications from us, please unsubscribe here, or the bottom of promotional emails you may receive from us or you can also contact us by writing to Privacy, Miva AK, Inc, 4600 Madison, 10th Floor, Kansas City, MO 64112. 

If you do opt out from receiving promotional communications from us, this does not prohibit us from sharing PII for non-marketing purposes listed above. 

Quiz Rocket also displays personalized third party advertising based on your PII. Advertisers may assume that users who interact with or click on a personalized advertisement meet their criteria to personalize the advertisement (e.g. all female users in California). If you do not want us to use your PII to allow third party advertisements to be personalized, please follow the opt out process below. 

If you do not wish to receive personalized advertising from us, please contact us in writing to Privacy, Miva AK, Inc, 4600 Madison, 10th Floor, Kansas City, MO 64112. 

**SMS Offering and Opt-out rights:** Some of our advertisers' offers may allow you to register for content to be delivered by SMS. By completing or submitting a registration form or partial registration form to these offers, you are consenting to receive SMS, wireless or other mobile offering to your cell phone. You understand that your wireless carrier's standard charges and rates apply to these messages. For SMS text messages, you may remove your information by replying "STOP", "END", or "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received and we will remove your personal information within 10 days of receiving such request.

## V. Third Parties

Quiz Rocket includes third party advertising and links to other websites. These third party websites and advertisers, or internet advertising companies working on their behalf, may deliver to your web browser many of the advertisements you see when you use the Website. They may also use cookies, Javascript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs) and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisement and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features they may use, and the privacy practices of these entities are not covered by this Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. 

If you want to prevent a third-party ad server and/or third-party service provider from sending and reading cookies on your computer or using any of the other features referred to above, currently you must visit each ad network's and service provider's website individually and opt out (if they offer this capability). Note that disabling cookies may limit, or in some cases, preclude your use of this site. 

Please remember that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by us at Quiz Rocket. On Quiz Rocket or within messages received from Quiz Rocket there may be embedded code or links to other third party websites (including Advertisers) that have different privacy and security policies. Quiz Rocket does not endorse, nor is Quiz Rocket responsible for the accuracy of these policies. The entities which advertise and/or place banner ads on Quiz Rocket including co-registration Advertisers are independent third parties and are not affiliated with Quiz Rocket. You should consult these third party sites for their policies. 

## VI. Security

Quiz Rocket has security measures in place to protect information against unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure, including a comprehensive information security program. Quiz Rocket uses industry-standard procedures and guidelines. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store PII. 

Quiz Rocket also ensures that all third parties who receive PII have in place reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information, to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure and that third party service providers maintain information security practices and programs in accordance with applicable law. 

We restrict access to PII to: key executives of Miva AK, Inc. and members of the development team (including employees, contractors and agents of Miva AK, Inc.) who have direct access to information under our control, who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our products and services; or persons who need to comply with record retention requirements by law. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations. 

Personal information collected on Quiz Rocket is stored in our system for a period of one year for administration purposes before being deleted automatically. 

## VII. Accessing and updating personal information 

Please contact us in writing to Privacy, Miva AK, Inc, 4600 Madison, 10th Floor, Kansas City, MO 64112 if you would like to access PII we have collected about you. We will make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your PII and either correct this data if it is inaccurate or delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask that you identify yourself and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. 

## VIII. Data integrity

We process PII only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on you to update or correct your personal information whenever necessary. 

## IX. Children 

Quiz Rocket does not knowingly collect personal information from minors under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide us with your personal information. If you have reason to believe that a child has provided us with their personal information, please contact us at the address given above and we will delete that information from our databases. 

Users under 13 years of age are not allowed to participate in quizzes or surveys offered by Quiz Rocket. Quiz Rocket is not responsible for information obtained from underage users who have provided false information regarding their age. However, in these instances parents may visit the Quiz Rocket Unsubscribe page to unsubscribe the child's email, and have his/her information removed. Quiz Rocket is not responsible for any offers presented to underage users who have provided false information regarding their age. Parents must contact offer providers directly. No information should be submitted to, or posted at, any Quiz Rocket Web sites by users under 13 years of age. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. 

## Your Acceptance of These Terms

If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you may unsubscribe from our services by completing an opt-out request at the following URL: 

Unsubscribe here!   

Alternatively, you may send postal mail to the following address: Quiz Rocket attn Privacy / Miva AK, Inc.  
4600 Madison, 10th Floor  
Kansas City, MO 64112  

Last updated 05/04/2012
